lovable: adj. 可爱的, eccentric: n.   （行为）古怪人
Lesson 31. A lovable eccentric. True eccentric's never deliberately set out to draw attention
第31课。可爱的古怪。真正的怪人从未故意引起注意
disregard: v.   不顾，漠视, convention: n.   习俗，风俗, conscious: adj. 感觉到的，意识到的
to themselves. They disregard social conventions without being conscious that they are doing
对自己。他们无视社会惯例，而没有意识到自己在做
invariably: adv. 总是，经常地
anything extraordinary. This invariably wins them the love and respect of others. For they
任何非凡的。这总是赢得他们他人的爱与尊重。因为他们
routine: n.   常规；惯例
add color to the dull routine of everyday life. Up to the time of his death. Richard Colson was
为日常生活的沉闷习惯增添色彩。直到他去世的时候。理查德·科尔森（Richard Colson）是
shrewd: adj. 精明的
one of the most notable figures in our town. He was a shrewd and wealthy businessman. But most
我们镇上最著名的人物之一。他是一位精明而富有的商人。但大多数
people in the town hardly knew anything about this side of his life. He was known to us all as
镇上的人们几乎对他一生的这一面一无所知。他被我们所有人都称为
eccentric: n.   （行为）古怪人, eccentricity: n.   怪僻, legendary: adj. 传奇般的, snob: n.   势利小人，谄上欺下的人
Dickey and his eccentricity had become legendary long before he died. Dickey dislikes snobbs
迪基（Dickey）和他的怪癖在他去世之前就已经成为传奇人物。Dickey不喜欢势利小人
intensely: adv. 强烈地
intensely, though he owned a large car. He hardly ever used it, preferring always to go on foot,
强烈地，尽管他拥有一辆大型汽车。他几乎从未使用过，更喜欢总是步行，
even when it was raining heavily. He refused to carry an umbrella. One day, he walked into an
即使下雨了。他拒绝携带雨伞。有一天，他走进了
expensive shop after having been caught in a particularly heavy shower. He wanted to buy a $300
昂贵的商店被送入特别沉重的淋浴间。他想买300美元
watch for his wife. But he was in such a bidraggled condition that an assistant refused to serve him.
看着他的妻子。但是他处于bidragggggggggg的状态，助手拒绝为他服务。
Dickey left the shop without a word and returned carrying a large cloth bag. As it was extremely
迪基一言不发地离开了商店，然后带着一个大布袋返回。因为这是非常
dump: v.   把……砰的一声抛下
heavy, he dumped it on the counter. The assistant asked him to leave. But Dickey paid no attention
沉重，他把它扔在柜台上。助手要求他离开。但是迪基没有注意
to him and requested to see the manager. Recognizing who the customer was, the manager was most
给他，并要求去看经理。认识到客户是谁，经理是最多的
apologetic: adj. 道歉的, reprimand: v.   训斥
apologetic and reprimanded the assistant severely. When Dickey was given the watch, the presented
道歉并严厉谴责助手。当迪基被给予手表时，提出了
the assistant with the cloth bag. It contained $300 in pennies. He insisted on the assistance
带布袋的助手。它包含300美元的便士。他坚持协助
counting the money before he left, 30,000 pennies in all. On another occasion, he invited a number
在他离开之前计算这笔钱，总共有30,000便士。在另一个场合，他邀请了一个号码
of important critics to see his private collection of modern paintings. This exhibition received a
重要的批评家看到他的私人绘画集。这个展览收到了
great deal of attention in the press. For though the pictures were supposed to be the work of famous
媒体上的关注很大。因为尽管图片应该是名人的作品
stage: v.   暗中策划, elaborate: adj. 精心构思的
artists, they had in fact been painted by Dickey. It took him four years to stage this elaborate
艺术家，他们实际上是由迪基（Dickey）绘制的。他花了四年的时间才登上这个精致的
joke simply to prove that critics do not always know what they are talking about.
只是为了证明批评家并不总是知道他们在说什么。